mobioinsider.com 2015-04-20

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
Last Modified November 11, 2013 - Version 4.0
Mobio (“Mobio”, “we”, “us” or “our”) has created this privacy policy (“Policy”) to demonstrate the
importance of protecting the private nature of your personal information.
This Policy describes the ways we collect information from and about you, and what we do with that
information, when you visit and use our website at [www.mobioinsider.com] (the “Site”), as well as any
related websites or obtain any products, services and/or content we offer (collectively with the Site called
our “Services”).
When you use the Services or otherwise provide us with your personal information, you are consenting to
the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of that information as described in
this Policy. Therefore, you should read this Policy carefully so that you can decide whether or not to
provide information to us.
You can choose not to provide certain information when using our Services, but then you might not be able
to take advantage of many features of those Services.
We are located at: #300 - 128 West Hastings Street, Vancouver BC, V6B 1G8, Canada
1.        What this Policy Covers
This Policy covers our treatment of information gathered when you are using or accessing the Services.
This Policy also covers our treatment of any information that our partners share with us or that we share
with our partners.
This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, including
but not limited to any third party websites, services and applications (“Third Party Services”) that you may
choose to access through the Service or to people that we don’t manage or employ. While we try to
provide access only to those Third Party Services that share our respect for your privacy, we don’t take
responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Third Party Services. We encourage you to
carefully review the privacy policies of all Third Party Services you choose to access.
Even though Mobio provides Services on a global basis to a global community, our operations are located
in Canada and our policies and procedures, including this Policy, are based on Canadian law. If you are
located outside of Canada, then your country’s laws governing data collection and use may differ from
Canadian law. By providing your personal information to us, you are consenting to the use of that
information as described in, and in accordance with this Policy, and to the transfer, storage and processing
of that information to and in Canada and/or other countries.
2.        Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access
You can access our Site home page and browse our Site without disclosing your personal information.
3.        What Information Do We Collect From You and How Do We Use It?
Your Account Information: When you create an account on a Mobio Service (an “Account”), you may
provide information such as your username, password and email address. You may also be required to
provide us with your birthdate, which we use to verify your age and may use to personalize the Services for
you (for example, by presenting you with content relevant to your age group). This information may
personally identify you. For example, if you use your full name as your username, you are disclosing your
CW6724211.1	  

identity to the public. We store all of this information securely and never reveal it to third parties without
your explicit consent.
Information about Your Accounts on Third Party Services: You can link your Account to certain
Third Party Services. By doing that, you will provide us with your username or other user ID on each of
those Third Party Services. You may also be required to engage in an authorization process with each of
those Third Party Services, where we receive a token that allows us to access those accounts so that we can,
for example, when you choose, enable you to post User Content (as defined in our Terms of Service) on
those services or provide links to your User Content to those services. We do not receive or store your
passwords for your Third Party Service accounts.
Information Obtained from Third Party Services: In some cases, when you connect your Account with
your accounts on Third Party Services, we may obtain information about you that you have chosen to make
available to those Third Party Services. To the extent we obtain such information, we may use it to
improve and personalize the Services. As a general practice, we strongly urge you to make careful
judgments about any personal information you disclose to Internet services, including Mobio and linked
Third Party Services, regardless of whether you choose to link your accounts together.
User Content: By default, all sharing through the Services is public, and when you provide us with User
Content it is published so that anyone can view it. User Content published and shared publicly is accessible
to everyone, including search engines, and you may lose any privacy rights you might have regarding that
content. In addition, information shared publicly may be copied and shared throughout the Internet,
including through features native to the Services. While you are free to remove published pieces of User
Content from or delete your Account, because of the nature of Internet sharing and technological
limitations inherent to the Services, copies of that content may exist elsewhere and be retained indefinitely,
including in our systems.
Information Related to Use of the Services: We collect information about how people use the Services,
including those with an Account. This information includes general usage information, and may include
information such as the number and frequency of our visitors, which pages or features of the Services they
have visited, which links on the Services they have clicked on and the length of those visits. We may also
use third party applications and services, such as Google Analytics, to collect and analyze this information.
This information enables us and third parties authorized by us to determine how often individuals use our
Services so that we can analyze and improve them. Some of this information may be associated with your
Account, such as the topics you search for and the help pages that you visit. We may also use some of this
information in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure related to all of our users that would not
identify you personally. We use information about your use of the Services to improve and enhance your
experience on the Services.
Web Browser Information: We automatically receive and record information from your web browser
when you use our Services, such as your browser type and version, the type of device you are using, your
operating system and version, your language preference, the website or service that referred you to the
Services, the date and time of each web request you make, your screen display information, and
information from any cookies we have placed on your web browser. We also sometimes detect whether you
are using certain web browser extensions and store that information in a manner associated with your
Account. Web browser-related information is used to enhance your experience with the Services (for
example, by personalization) and to allow us to improve the Services; but none of this information is used
in a manner that would identify you personally.
Your IP Address: We collect IP addresses through our Site. An IP address is a number that is
automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing the web. Web servers, the computers
that “serve up” web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address, and when you request a
page from our Site, our servers log your IP address. Our Site does not link IP addresses to anything
personally identifiable, so although your session will be logged, you will remain anonymous to us. This
aggregated information is used to improve the function of our Site and may be shared with third parties.
CW6724211.1	  

4.        Children’s Privacy
We do not direct any of our Services specifically at children who are less than 13 years old, nor do we
knowingly collect personal information from children who are less than 13 years old. We will promptly
delete any personal information that we have collected about a user who is less than 13 years old if we
become aware that we have collected such information, but otherwise we do not take specific steps to
protect the privacy of children who disclose their personal data to us.
5.        How Is Your Information Shared?
We never share information we receive from you unless: (a) we have your permission to share that
information; (b) we have given you prior notice that the information will be shared, and with whom; or (c)
that information is aggregate information or other information that does not identify you.
Public Disclosure of Your Information Through the Services: By default, content published through
the Services is shared with the public, and this is an important feature of the Services. Because this kind of
information can be seen by anyone and may be indexed by search engines, you should be careful what you
choose to disclose publicly and make sure it is information you want to share with everyone.
Information You Share with Third Party Services: You may access Third Party Services through the
Services, for example by clicking on externally-pointing links. You may also choose to share information
that you provide to us with those Third Party Services (for example, by syndicating posts to Twitter or
Facebook). This Policy only governs information we collect and you are responsible for reading and
understanding the privacy policies in effect for those Third Party Services.
Information Shared To Operate and Improve the Services: In some cases, we share information that
we store (such as IP Addresses) with third parties, such as our service providers, consultants and other
agents (“Agents”), for the purposes of operating and improving the Services. Our Agents are generally
bound by confidentiality obligations and, unless we tell you differently, they do not have any right to use
any of the information we share with them beyond the scope and duration of what is necessary to help us.
You hereby consent to our sharing of your information with our Agents.
Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others: To the extent reasonable, we
try to protect our community from baseless legal demands. However, we reserve the right to access,
preserve and disclose any information that we reasonably believe is necessary, in our sole discretion, to:
(a) satisfy any law, regulation, legal process, governmental request or governmental order; (b) enforce this
Policy and our Terms of Service, including any investigation of potential violations; (c) detect, prevent or
otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues (including exchanging information with other
companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam/malware prevention); (d) respond to user
support requests; or (e) protect the rights, property, health or safety of us, our users, any third parties or the
public in general, including but not limited to situations involving possible violence, suicide, or self-harm.
With Your Consent or at Your Request: If you ask us to release information that we have about your
Account, we will do so if reasonable and not unduly burdensome.
6.        Confidentiality / Security
Your Account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You must take
reasonable steps to prevent unauthorized access to your Account and personal information by taking
appropriate measures to select and protect your password and limiting access to your computer and browser
by signing off after you have finished accessing your Account.
We seek to protect your information (including your Account information) to ensure that it is kept private;
however, we can’t guarantee the security of any information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or
software failure and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time.
CW6724211.1	  

7.       Access to Information We May Have About You
If you have an Account, you can access and delete most information associated with your Account by
logging into the Services and checking your Account Settings page. You can also ask us if we have any
other personal information about you by sending us an email to support@mobioinsider.com. If you send us
an email, we will provide you with a copy of the personal information we have about you in our possession,
almost instantaneously, although we may first require proof of your identity. We will provide this
information to you free of charge.
We reserve the right to refuse to provide our visitors with a copy of their personal information, but will
give reasons for our refusal. Visitors have the right to challenge our decision to refuse to provide them
with a copy of their personal information.
We allow all users of our Services to challenge the information we hold about them and, where appropriate,
you may have your information erased, rectified or amended or completed.
8.       What Happens When Your Account is Deleted?
If you delete your Account in accordance with our Terms and Conditions, we will take reasonable steps to
remove all of your personal information from our production servers. However, you understand that your
personal information may not be fully removed from our systems, as certain information temporarily stored
(“cached”) on our systems and back-up copies of or references to your Account information (not available
to others) may not be immediately removed. To the extent we retain any of your personal information, the
terms of this Policy will continue to apply to us with respect to that information as required by applicable
law, even after you have deleted your Account.
9.       Privacy Compliance
Our privacy policy is compliant with the laws of Canada. It is also compliant with the OECD Privacy
guidelines.
In order to demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with those laws and guidelines, we are voluntarily
committed to a Self Assessment procedure. The designation of our privacy policy person is Privacy
Officer, mobioinsider.com/privacy
10. Changes to This Policy
We may amend this Policy from time to time, using the process for modifications set forth in our Terms of
Service. Use of information we collect now is subject to the version of the Policy in effect at the time such
information is used.
CW6724211.1
